Are you looking down while watching this video?
Let's dig into the shocking truth and perfect cure for text neck syndrome,
a modern disease caused by smartphones.
If the angle increases to a 60-degree steep tilt,
the load skyrockets to about 27 kilograms.
This is an immense physical shock,
equivalent to carrying a seven-year-old child on the back of your neck all day.
However, without lifestyle correction, treatment is in vain.
The Don'ts!
Lying face down using your phone,
or placing the monitor low and sticking your neck out like a turtle are absolute strict no-nos.
Now the Do's you must practice!
Align the top of your monitor exactly to your eye level,
and when using a smartphone,
support your elbow with the other hand and raise the device to your eye level.